thecro.com 2016-11-05

# Privacy Policy - CR Magazine

At the same time that CRO Corp, LLC is committed to bringing you information tailored to your individual needs, we recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about you, our customers and prospects. In adopting this customer privacy policy, our intent is to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using information with your reasonable expectations of privacy.

CRO Corp, LLC does not collect personally identifying information about individuals, except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals.

Web servers serving CRO Corp, LLC automatically collect information about which pages each user visits and the domain name of visitors. This is used for internal review, to tailor information to individual visitors and for traffic audits. We also provide this information (as well as information from third-party market researchers) about our users on an aggregated, anonymous basis to our advertisers. Any personally identifiable information provided by subscribers online as part of an advertiser promotion online (i.e. online coupons) may be provided directly to advertisers.

CRO Corp, LLC may place a “cookie” on the browser of a CRO Corp, LLC user’s computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information. A cookie can be used to tell when your computer has contacted a Web site; we use the information for editorial purposes and for other purposes such as delivery of ads, so we can customize delivery of information without compromising privacy. For example, cookies are used to ensure that you don’t see the same ad too many times in a single session.

A user’s personally identifiable information (e.g., name, e-mail address) may be used by CRO Corp, LLC for editorial purposes. For example, we may use information provided by you to us as part of an editorial online survey. If we run competitions or contests on the site, you may be required to provide information such as your telephone number and address in order to participate. The exact rules may vary in each case but the specific rules for any contest will state how that information may be used. We also may use personally identifiable information for marketing and promotional purposes. We may send you e-mails about CRO Corp, LLC products, promotions, or services as well as on behalf of other companies.

Except as stated in this privacy policy or at the time of collection, user’s personally identifiable information, will not be transferred to a party outside CRO Corp, LLC, its divisions, its vendors providing Internet hosting services or third party list managers unless stated at the time of collection. If you do not wish to receive any e-mail or to have us share such information with another party, you may “opt out” at any time by e-mailing us or contacting us by regular mail.

We do not control the privacy policies of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide hyperlinks. CRO Corp, LLC users should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in chat areas or bulletin boards, that information may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages from others.

Technology on the Internet is developing at a rapid pace, and we need to maintain our flexibility in the online arena. If we need to change our policy in the future, we will post these changes as soon as they go into effect.
